Excuse me, sir. Sir, is this your Rolls Royce?
Yes.
And what line of business are you in? What did
you do to be able to afford a Rolls Royce?
I own the world's largest water park.
You own the world's largest water park?
My nickname is Aquaman.
Who am I here with today?
Jason Derulo.
What was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
$30 million.
Are you a business owner?
I am. So I own about 13 businesses now.
13 companies?
Yes, sir.
What business has made you the most money?
You'll never be able to guess.
What was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
I mean, it's hundreds of millions.
$30 million this year.
Did you buy this Rolls Royce cash?
Yeah. So we're here in Dubai, and
in Dubai, a lot of transactions happen cash.
So literally $600,000 bricks of cash.
What's a lesson about money that
banks don't want people to know?
Banks?
I'll tell you something.
You guys, we just landed in
the supercar capital of the world.
And no, I don't mean camels. I mean actual supercars.
Guys, we're in Dubai.
We're in Dubai right now.
And today, I'm going to be going
all over the wealthiest areas in Dubai
to find supercar owners, to figure out what they did
to be able to afford supercars from
Rolls Royces to Ferraris to G-Wagons, everything.
This video is going to be
amazing from start to finish, you guys.
So you're going to want to stay tuned.
But with that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
Is this your G-Wagon?
Yeah, I made it.
And what did you do to
be able to afford a G-Wagon?
I made a G-Wagon out here in the UAE.
I own the world's largest water park.
You own the world's largest water park?
My nickname is Aquaman.
Yeah?
Basically.
How long have you been a business owner?
More than a decade.
And I go all over the
world interviewing the most successful entrepreneurs.
Could I interview you for the channel real quick?
We have five minutes.
Let's do five minutes.
Have you ever been broke before?
I was bankrupt twice, sued 24 times.
You were bankrupt twice.
And sued 24 times.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, my goodness.
How did you come back from that?
Again, the genius thing is never quit.
People think I'm from here.
I'm born and raised from the UAE.
Oh, you're born with money.
You have all money.
I mean, I wish that was
the story, but that wasn't the case.
So you don't come from money?
No, no, I don't.
My family was nice people,
mid-class, one job all their life.
And then I was the black sheep.
I said, no, I'm going to be different.
And that's how it became.
But yeah, bankrupt twice.
I still remember I got
once a text on my phone.
I had $1.8 million in negative.
For the next four years, I'm just paying back debts that
my partner that was with me in the business got us in.
And then eventually it became now
the biggest one in the world.
Why did you get sued 24 times?
Suppliers, old partner, third party suppliers, employees.
Different things.
Because when you're in business,
people always want to sue you.
So how important is it
to choose the right business partner?
It is the most important thing.
Now I'm playing solo.
All my companies, I do joint ventures with people.
Do you prefer it that way to have complete ownership?
Personally, yes.
Why is that?
Because I've had bad experiences with partners.
Because again, I am very aggressive in business.
I'm very open for failure.
I love failing.
I have failed and love and failing for so long.
So for me, most people are scared of losing money.
For me, it's just money.
It's like, so what?
It's just money.
Let's make more of it.
Because I know how it feels
to have money and not have money.
I've been both spectrums of the equation.
But you failed a lot as an entrepreneur.
Oh yeah.
My first year, I was rejected 617 times.
First year.
617 times?
Every day, I was getting at least two no's.
Every no is one step closer to 20.
Exactly.
Now I know how to navigate them much faster.
And again, all these no's built me
up to become what I am right now.
I would never look back and
say, oh, I was horrible at this.
That's the best lesson I've ever had.
What's the deepest life quote that you've ever heard?
Something that I wrote to myself, actually.
This is something I want to show you.
I wrote this to myself eight years ago
when I had three legal cases on me.
And I was, I think,
a quarter million dollars in debt.
Train your mind harder than anybody.
Never accept someone else's limitation.
Pain is essential.
Visualize what you want all the time.
Learn the meaning of overload.
Become obsessed.
Never become satisfied.
That was me eight years ago.
So it seems like the mindset is everything.
It's the only thing.
More important than skill sets.
Skill sets, you can always gain them.
But the mindset, again, you either
have it or you don't have it.
You can't be motivated all day.
But you need to be disciplined.
Yeah.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Thank you so much for your time, man.
Thank you.
Appreciate you.
You need to come to the water park.
Let's go.
Guys, that's got to be one
of the wildest walk-ups I've ever done.
He owns.
The largest water park in the entire world.
But I want to highlight how there's a
big misconception about wealth in the Middle East.
Everybody thinks that just because you live in
places like Dubai and the UAE that you
come from a ton of money.
He wasn't born into a super rich or wealthy family.
But all he did was
not take no for an answer.
He was rejected 600 times in a single year.
But he kept his head down.
He kept going.
Learned how to sell.
And ended up making eight figures in a single year.
Great interview out here in Dubai.
We got to keep this video
rolling and go find another one.
Come on.
Let's go, you guys.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, is this your Rolls Royce?
Yes.
And what line of business are you in?
What did you do to be
able to afford a Rolls Royce?
So I own a fashion brand called Icon.
You're a business owner?
Yeah.
How long have you been an entrepreneur?
Six years.
Over these six years, what's the most amount
of money you've made in a single year?
$30 million this year.
$30 million.
Can I go all over the
world interviewing the biggest business owners?
Could I get one quick minute
with you for the channel real quick?
Yeah.
Would you do it outside of the car?
Sure.
Did you buy this Rolls Royce cash?
Yeah.
So we're here in Dubai.
And in Dubai, a lot of transactions happen cash.
So literally $600,000 bricks of cash.
So you bought this for $600,000?
Yeah.
That's incredible.
So what is the deepest
life quote that you've ever heard?
Whatever you want, you can have it.
As long as you're willing
to bleed for what you're asking.
So bleed for what you're asking?
Yes.
You got to put it all on the table.
If you can have it all.
And I'm here because I'm willing to sacrifice who I am
right now for who I want to be in the future.
And most people, they don't want to trade their
current life for who they want to be later.
I'm willing to lock myself in, go monk mode.
Don't see fear.
Friends for six months.
Don't be with no chicks.
I didn't care.
I only cared about who I had to become.
And everything has a price.
Your dream life has a price too.
So the question is, are
you willing to pay that price?
To me, the answer was yes every fucking time.
When you were coming up, did
you have a lot of haters?
Too much.
Yeah.
And still do.
Look, if you don't want any haters,
then becoming successful is not for you.
Because it's a part of it.
But in the beginning, it's more people
hate on what they gave up on themselves.
So if they see you trying to pursue that business,
you trying to become rich,
for yourself,
and they've not had the balls to try it,
or they're just scared,
then they will try to talk you down, you know?
And to me, that was really hard in the beginning.
But I'm very happy that inside
my mind, I'm a very stubborn kid.
So if someone says to me,
you can do it, don't do it,
I want it twice as much.
I was like, fuck it.
I will prove all these motherfuckers wrong.
In school, even close family members,
maybe sometimes even the people you love,
or the people that love you,
will talk down on you.
And you just have to think like,
once I'm successful,
I will show them.
And that's exactly what I did.
And I can tell you
with the hand on my heart,
there's no better feeling than proving
the ones wrong that doubted you.
You guys, this video has been insane.
And we're on our way to
go get our next interview right now.
But I want to take a quick moment
to let you guys know a very important,
a very special announcement.
So a couple months ago,
I launched and built one of the biggest,
one of the greatest entrepreneur
communities in the entire world.
And you can join this community today for free.
Inside of this community,
every single week,
I host live calls with the biggest business,
business owners in the world,
even billionaires,
where they come in on these calls
and directly mentor all of our members,
where they teach them skills like how to sell,
how to market,
how to negotiate,
how to start and scale a business,
how to invest and make your money work for you.
For example,
we had Todd Napola who owns
over $500 million worth of real estate.
He taught our community how to invest
in real estate without having any money to
your name.
Or how about Steven Klubeck who sold
his company to Hilton for $2.2 billion.
He taught our community how
to sell and how to negotiate,
like a billionaire.
You guys,
the only shortcut to success in
today's world isn't having rich parents.
It isn't luck.
It isn't even hard work.
It's mentorship.
It's finding the people that are in the
exact same places that you want to be
and learning everything you possibly can from them.
So once again,
if you want to join the community today for free,
all you have to do is go down to
the link in the description of this video and
join the school of mentors.
I can't wait to see you
on the inside of the community.
It's going to be incredible.
With that being said,
let's get back to the video.
Guys,
I've got a very special,
surprise for you all right now.
We're headed to go interview Jason Derulo,
one of the most successful musicians
turned entrepreneurs in the entire world.
He's made hundreds of millions of dollars
throughout his career in both music and
in business and currently owns over 10 companies.
So we're going to go interview him and
ask him how he created his wealth and how
you can do the exact same thing just like him.
So let's go talk to Jason
and see what he has to say.
Who am I here with today?
Jason Derulo.
What was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
Most amount of money that
I've made in a single year,
$30 million.
For those that don't know,
what industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
So I started off in music.
Music was my first four
way into any kind of success.
You know,
I was obsessed with music as a kid.
Are you a business owner?
I am.
So I own about 13 businesses now.
13 companies.
Yes, sir.
What business has made you the most money?
You'd never be able to guess.
What business?
Car washes.
How many car washes do you own?
So I own about 65 car washes now.
65 car washes.
Why are car washes so profitable?
Car washes are amazing because essentially,
you're owning a piece of land, right?
So obviously you're going to be making
money on that car wash every single day.
Everybody washes their car.
Their car is their pride and joy.
Even during the pandemic,
people were washing their cars.
Ain't had nowhere to go,
but still was washing their cars.
It's the one thing that when we leave
home is a representation of who we are
and what our level of success is.
So it's profitable from that standpoint,
but also it just being real estate,
you know,
as time progresses,
it just appreciates in value,
especially if you're able to make car
washes like we've made and we've just
been able to,
just have way better customer service than everybody.
We pay attention to details.
So every customer experience,
we treat it like it's our
last chance at having that customer,
right?
I mean,
that's all about customer experience.
So in other words,
they're recession proof.
Recession proof.
I mean,
so far,
so far it's been a recession proof.
It's been pandemic proof.
I mean,
if you can make it through the pandemic,
you can make it through anything.
As a multimillionaire,
what is your best negotiation
advice for anybody in business?
Oh,
I got,
I got those shits for days.
So one of the key negotiation tactics,
damn,
I'm about to give up my game.
Come on.
This is wild.
Um,
okay.
So a big,
big,
big one is allowing other
people to make the offer first.
A lot of times you can shoot yourself
in the foot and aim lower than you thought
that you can get.
So for me,
I always have somebody else make the offer first.
And sometimes I'm just shocked at what the number is.
I'm like,
damn,
well shit,
I'm glad I let you answer first.
Cause I was going to go here and then you,
you know,
sometimes that number can even double,
so that's a big,
big,
big one that has been a game changer for me.
Another negotiation piece of advice.
Sometimes taking a breather from
the situation is a good thing.
What I mean is,
so you'll,
you'll have a conversation,
initial conversation.
You'll have gotten their offer.
Then you reciprocate,
right?
With something higher.
Always,
you know,
you always got to say something higher.
Well,
I was thinking more of this that,
uh,
and if you guys cannot come to a,
an agreement,
let a little time pass,
let two days pass and
then come back to the situation.
Don't come back begging really quickly.
I treat it as if it's a relationship almost,
you know,
be desperate.
You cannot be desperate.
Um,
and I,
I,
I think,
you know,
coming from a position of power is always
the better route as opposed to coming in,
asking for something.
How old are you now?
If you were to go back in time and
have a conversation with your 20 year old self,
when you were starting from zero,
what's the best piece of advice that
you give to your 20 year old self?
Which are not changing.
You're choosing.
Break that down.
If you feel like you're overweight and you're not
doing anything to change that you're choosing to be overweight.
If you don't feel like you have enough money and
you're not trying to change that you're choosing to be broke.
Guys,
that was an amazing interview with Jason Derulo,
$30 million in a single year.
And he just gave some of
the best negotiation advice I've ever heard.
You guys got to realize he's been at the
table with the biggest people in the music industry.
Now business doing 30 million in a year.
Crazy interview,
crazy snack out here in Dubai.
You guys,
we've got to keep this video rolling.
Go get another one.
This video has been crazy.
Come on.
What was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
I mean,
it's hundreds of millions.
What's a lesson about money that
banks don't want people to know.
Banks.
Yeah.
Could they pay?
I'll tell you something.
Look,
if a bank says I'm only going to take
1% of your money for managing all your things,
that's not 1% of your money.
That's probably 95% of your income that
you would have had in your lifetime.
Now you're like,
how does that make sense?
It makes a lot of sense because this is one of the tricks
that people that are not into finances or generally anybody who pays taxes,
let's call it taxes because banks
fees could also be called taxes.
Right?
Think about this.
If you live in a country that takes 25% income tax and you start
with a dollar and over your lifetime you double this dollar over 20 periods,
just just a numbers example,
you would have $1,048,000,
right?
That's just over 20 days,
let's say,
or 20 years.
However you want to see it.
If you double that dollar for 20 times,
you will end up with $1,048,000.
Now,
how much would you have if somebody
took 25% from your profits after the same?
Same period around 750,000 whatever.
No,
you would have 96% less.
You would have around 50 to $70,000
because they took away your compounding effect.
That is the trick.
So is the base doesn't grow that fast
and you will feel it at the end.
The compounding comes with the growing base.
They don't teach that in school.
You know that,
right?
I don't know why.
What's your best negotiation advice for anybody in business?
Cause you've been at the table with some heavy hitters.
I know that you exited a
company for a lot of money.
What's your best negotiation advice for anybody?
Business negotiations are won by the
people who don't need the deal.
Look,
just walk away,
but you're always in some kind of a
situation where you might really need to do,
especially when you don't have a lot,
you might really need the deal.
So I was in a situation actually quite recently,
four or five years ago,
I was sitting in front of investors,
right?
We had a good business,
but we needed those investors cause we're going into
a market where they were kind of very powerful.
And they said,
Hey,
there's a clause that we
want to have in the contract.
And I,
I didn't want that clause.
So it was already eight to
nine months into a deal negotiation.
It's bankers sitting there,
lawyers sitting here and their lawyers are
sitting there and it's a very tense situation.
And the deal is about to break and
it's really a lot of money on the table.
So I said,
uh,
we have to change the clause.
We can't do this deal.
It was bad for the shareholders.
And as a CEO,
you are kind of the representative of all shareholders.
And then they said,
we have the money.
So we have the muscle.
I asked for a break.
I went out with my lawyers and my bankers.
I said,
I think the deal is off.
And they're like,
you crazy.
What are you doing?
We've been working for so long.
I said,
okay,
I have a situation.
I have a solution.
So I went back into the boardroom and I said,
guys,
what kind of CEO do you want to have tomorrow?
You will be my shareholders as well.
So if you're my shareholder,
you want to see you
who gives in and gives up.
If somebody says something like this,
or you want to see
you who stands up and says,
this is not good for our shareholders.
And I'm not going to do this deal.
You might have them.
Yeah.
I have the muscles,
but I have the balls.
And I was quiet.
And they actually looked at it
from that perspective now and say,
yeah,
he's kind of right.
So if he's now kind of weak in our negotiation,
but tomorrow he's our CEO.
I don't want to see you like that.
I want a strong CEO.
So that was one of the
things that I learned later on.
Be diplomatic,
never be disrespectful,
but put yourself into their shoes after the deal.
That's really what helped.
You got amazing advice,
man.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate that.
Thank you guys.
This video was incredible.
It's a make,
we've got to come back out to Dubai
very soon because the content out here is
amazing,
but I need you guys to like,
and subscribe for amazing content.
We've got coming very soon.
And if you're not a member yet,
you guys need to join my private entrepreneur community,
the school of mentors,
the links down in the description of
this video to join because members in our
community can hop on live calls
and ask questions directly to the millionaires
and the billionaires that I interview
about how to start and scale their
businesses,
the skill sets they need to develop like sales negotiation,
other things like how to grow,
create wealth and real estate in various other industries.
You do not want to miss out on this opportunity.
So to join,
like I said,
go to the link down
in the description of this video.
I can't wait to see on the inside,
but with that being said,
I'll see you in the next video.